https://vartechsystems.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy and Information Collected by VarTech Systems Inc.
800-223-8050Follow Us:MENUMENUHome Products
DiamondVueRugged Monitors and Panel PC’s All-WeatherIP67 Waterproof Monitors and Panel PC’s ToughStationFully-Sealed Monitors and Panel PC’s Small Form Factor ComputersIndustrial Grade SFF and Mini PC’sHazardous Area SolutionsSunlight ReadableMilitaryMarineLarge Format DisplaysEnvironmental & Functional Upgrade Packages Industrial Pedestal Mounts Industrial Mounting Arms Rugged Keyboard Solutions Solutions
Oil & Gas
Military
Marine
Hazardous Area Solutions Special Process Control Displays Custom Solutions Large Format Solutions Panel Mounting Solutions Sunlight Readable Monitors and Displays Touch Screen Technology LCD Optical Bonding (VBOND) Environmental & Functional Upgrade Packages Support Repair & Retrofit Services Frequently Asked Questions Discontinued Products Touch Drivers Helpful Links About VarTech Capability Statement Certifications Quality Standards Contact Customer Feedback RMA Request Careers
Privacy PolicyHome Privacy PolicyVarTech Systems Privacy PolicyOur Online Privacy Policy:This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.vartechsystems.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Registration In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.Cookies We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediatelyvia telephone at 800-223-8050 or via email using our Contact Form. Engineered, Fabricated and Assembled in the USA
Contact a specialist today for information on our complete line of industrial grade displays and computer solutions.Toll-Free: (U.S. & Canada) 800-223-8050 | Contact Our Sales Team 11422 Industriplex Blvd. Baton Rouge, Louisiana 70809, U.S.PHONE: Toll-Free: (U.S. & Canada) 800-223-8050 Fax: 225-297-2440EMAIL: Email Our Sales TeamProductsDiamondVueAll-WeatherToughStationSmall Form Factor ComputersSolutionsSunlight ReadableMilitaryMarineHazardous AreaCustom SolutionsSupport & ResourcesRepair & Retrofit ServicesCustomer FeedbackRMA RequestCertificationsCareersFollow Us:
You have already registered Sign-Up for Product Updates
© 2020 Rugged Monitors and Panel Computers from Vartech. All Rights Reserved.Legal & DisclaimerPrivacy PolicyFollow Us:
We use cookiesWe use cookies and other tracking technologies to improve your browsing experience on our website, to analyze our website traffic, and to understand where our visitors are coming from. By browsing our website, you consent to our use of cookies and other tracking technologies. The forms on this site are for VarTech Systems communication with our customers for service and marketing purposes. No information will be transferred or sold.OkPrivacy policy
